Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES VI. Regions, 1964-1980
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VI. REGIONS
  - Southwest Region
    - Texas
      - Library
        - 1970-73 (Box 189, Folder 33-35)
      - Family Planning Services Available to Migratory Farm Workers in U.S. 1970 (Box 189, Folder 36)
      - Family Planning Services Available to Migratory Farm Workers, Mid-Continent 1969 (Box 189, Folder 37)
      - Migrant Project
        - Advisory Council 1970-71 (Box 189, Folder 38)
        - General 1970-72 (Box 189, Folder 39-40)
        - Conference 1969 (Box 189, Folder 41)
        - Progress Report 1971 (Box 189, Folder 42)
        - Travel & Family Planning Survey Instrument 1969 (Box 189, Folder 43)
      - Workshops
        - Miscellaneous 1975 (Box 189, Folder 44)
        - I & E Conference, Austin 1973-74 (Box 189, Folder 45)
        - General 1966-74 (Box 189, Folder 46-50)
        - Regional 1964-65 (Box 189, Folder 51)
        - Uniform Accounting 1967-68 (Box 189, Folder 52)
  - South Central Region
    - Texas
      - Affiliation & Financial Data 1977-80 (Box 189, Folder 53)
      - Alien Immigration Project 1978 (Box 189, Folder 54)
      - Committees 1978-80 (Box 189, Folder 55-56)
      - Correspondence 1977-81 (Box 189, Folder 57)
      - Consultants 1978-80 (Box 189, Folder 58)
      - Medical Committee 1978-80 (Box 189, Folder 59)
      - Executive Directors Organization 1978 (Box 189, Folder 60)
      - Leases 1978-80 (Box 189, Folder 61)
      - Memos 1977-80 (Box 189, Folder 62)
      - Personnel: Employment, Leaves, Vacations, Overtime, Resignations, etc. 1978-80 (Box 190, Folder 1)
      - Department Health, Education & Welfare, Family Planning Service 1980 (Box 190, Folder 2)
      - Public Affairs 1978-80 (Box 190, Folder 3)
      - Regional Chairman and/or Representative Correspondence 1978 (Box 190, Folder 4)
      - Regional Representative Project, Multi Media Slide/Board Development 1978 (Box 190, Folder 5)
      - Regional Representative's Report
        - National Board of Directors meetings 1978 (Box 190, Folder 6)
        - PPFA Executive Committee Meetings 1978 (Box 190, Folder 7)
      - Reports
        - General 1978-80 (Box 190, Folder 8-9)
        - Members 1978-79 (Box 190, Folder 10)
      - Surveys 1979 (Box 190, Folder 11)
      - System for Internal Information Flow 1979 (Box 190, Folder 12)
      - Central Region, Task Forces 1980 (Box 190, Folder 13)
      - Technical Assistance 1979 (Box 190, Folder 14)
      - Regional Conferences
        - Omaha Hilton Hotel, Omaha, Nebraska 1979 (Box 190, Folder 15)
        - Paso Del Norte Hotel, El Paso, Texas 1977-78 (Box 190, Folder 16)
      - Workshops
        - Medical Standards Workshop 1978 (Box 190, Folder 17)
        - Fort Worth, Texas 1980 (Box 190, Folder 18)
        - Miscellaneous 1978-80 (Box 190, Folder 19)
      - Abortion, Miscellaneous, Correspondence
        - 1971-74 (Box 190, Folder 20)
        - 1975 (Box 190)
      - Library, PPWP Chronological, Librarians' Correspondence, from 1/9/75 1975-76 (Box 190, Folder 21)
      - Affiliates
        - Certification Area/Turf Area, A Survey of Information 1974 (Box 190, Folder 22)
        - Fund Raising, Affiliate & Regional Totals 1970 (Box 190, Folder 23)
        - Personnel Survey 1972 (Box 190, Folder 24)
      - Affiliation & Financial Data
        - 1975-77 (Box 190, Folder 25-27)
        - 1964-74 (Box 190, Folder 28-37)
      - Committees
        - 1975-77 (Box 190, Folder 38-39)
        - 1970-74 (Box 190, Folder 40)
        - Medical
          - 1977 (Box 190, Folder 41)
          - 1972-74 (Box 190, Folder 42)
          - 1975-76 (Box 190)
          - 1974 (Box 190, Folder 43)
          - 1977 (Box 190)
        - PERC (Public Education & Research Committee)
          - 1974 (Box 190, Folder 44)
          - 1975 (Box 190)
      - Program Committee, Minutes 1975 (Box 190, Folder 45)
      - Regional Review Committee, Minutes
        - 1973 (Box 190, Folder 46)
        - 1977 (Box 190)
      - "The Components of a Thoroughly Adequate Planned Parenthood Affiliate," 1973 (Box 190, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence
        - 1976-79 (Box 190, Folder 48-49)
        - Alan P. Bloebaum, Director
          - 1975 (Box 190, Folder 50)
          - 1964-74 (Box 190, Folder 51-61)
      - Affiliates Operating on OEO Funds 1970 (Box 190, Folder 62)
      - Center, Daily Encounter Log 1972 (Box 190, Folder 63)
      - Educational Program Questionnaire, Temporary Folder 1973 (Box 190, Folder 64)
      - Executive Directors' Council 1973 (Box 190, Folder 65)
      - Dr. A. F. Guttmacher's Trip 1964-66 (Box 190, Folder 66)
      - Fund Raising Seminars 1973 (Box 190, Folder 67)
      - Executive committee meeting 1970 (Box 190, Folder 68)
      - Rev. Bruce Galloway
        - 1974 (Box 190, Folder 69)
        - 1975-76 (Box 190)
      - Group Purchase Plan: Gentec
        - 1974 (Box 190, Folder 70)
        - 1975 (Box 190)
      - Leases
        - 1974 (Box 190, Folder 71)
        - 1976 (Box 190)
    - Legality of Salaried Medical Directors for Texas PP Affiliates 1973 (Box 190, Folder 72)
    - Legal Counsel
      - 1974 (Box 190, Folder 73)
      - 1975-76 (Box 190)
      - Walter Zivley 1970-74 (Box 190, Folder 74)
    - "Management Action Line," 1977 (Box 190, Folder 75)
      - Mass Purchase of Clinic Supplies 1972-74 (Box 190, Folder 76)
      - Mid-Continent Fund-Raising Seminar, Dallas 1973 (Box 190, Folder 77)
      - OEO Regional Training Center, Galveston 1971-72 (Box 190, Folder 78)
      - Orientation for Executive Directors 1975 (Box 191, Folder 1)
      - Organizational Chart 1973 (Box 191, Folder 2)
      - Personnel: Employment, Vacations, Overtimes, Leaves, Terminations, etc.
        - 1972-74 (Box 191, Folder 3)
        - 1975-78 (Box 191)
      - Planning Guide 1973 (Box 191, Folder 4)
      - Earl Palmer, Resources Consultant 1972-74 (Box 191, Folder 5)
      - Projects & Project Development 1969-72 (Box 191, Folder 6)
      - Proposed AMA "Quality of Life" Seminar 1972-73 (Box 191, Folder 7)
      - Public Affairs
        - 1973-74 (Box 191, Folder 8)
        - 1975 (Box 191)
        - Strategies Meeting, Denver 1973 (Box 191, Folder 9)
      - Publicity
        - 1964-71 (Box 191, Folder 10)
        - 1977 (Box 191)
      - Reports
        - Affiliation Committee 1972 (Box 191, Folder 11)
        - General 1977 (Box 191, Folder 12)
        - Alan P. Bloebaum, Director
          - 1973-74 (Box 191, Folder 13)
          - 1975-76 (Box 191)
          - 1964-73 (Box 191, Folder 14-19)
        - Members
          - 1970-74 (Box 191, Folder 20)
          - 1975-77 (Box 191)
          - 1964-69 (Box 191, Folder 21)
          - 1976 (Box 191)
      - Regional Chairman and/or Representative, Correspondence
        - 1970-74 (Box 191, Folder 22)
        - 1975-77 (Box 191)
      - Regional Chairman's Report
        - 1972-74 (Box 191, Folder 23)
        - 1975-77 (Box 191)
      - Regional Chairman/Representative's Report of Annual Meeting 1973 (Box 191, Folder 24)
      - Regional Representative's Report
        - PPWP Executive Committee & Regional Representatives Meetings
          - 1970-74 (Box 191, Folder 25)
          - 1976-78 (Box 191)
        - National Board Meetings
          - 1973 (Box 191, Folder 26)
          - 1977 (Box 191)
        - Regional Director's Report
          - 1973 (Box 191, Folder 27)
          - 1975-76 (Box 191)
      - Sample Project Plans 1970 (Box 191, Folder 28)
      - Sowexco
        - General Correspondence 1970-74 (Box 191, Folder 29)
        - Report on Pap Smears in Affiliates in Southwest Region 1971 (Box 191, Folder 30)
        - Meeting, Albuquerque 1971 (Box 191, Folder 31)
        - Meeting, Waco, Texas 1971 (Box 191, Folder 32)
      - State, Legal Counsels 1973 (Box 191, Folder 33)
      - Summary of Data: Services, Cost & Distribution of Pap Smears 1970 (Box 191, Folder 34)
      - Technical Assistance 1968-73 (Box 191, Folder 35)
      - Annual Meeting
        - Waco, Texas 1977 (Box 191, Folder 36)
        - Lubbock, Texas 1976 (Box 191, Folder 37)
        - Houston, Texas
          - 1974 (Box 191, Folder 37a)
          - 1975-76 (Box 191)
        - Laredo, Texas 1973-74 (Box 191, Folder 38)
        - Tulsa, Oklahoma 1972-73 (Box 191, Folder 39)
        - Fort Worth, Texas 1971-72 (Box 191, Folder 40)
        - Albuquerque, New Mexico 1971 (Box 191, Folder 41)
        - Corpus Christi, Texas 1969-70 (Box 191, Folder 42)
      - Dr. Gordon Perkin's Trip 1964-65 (Box 191, Folder 43)
  - Western Region
    - California
      - Abortion
        - General Correspondence
          - 1971-74 (Box 191, Folder 44)
          - 1975-79 (Box 191)
        - Project 1972-73 (Box 191, Folder 45)
      - Affiliate, Medical Reviews 1977 (Box 191, Folder 46)
      - Affiliation & Financial Data
        - 1975-78 (Box 191, Folder 47-49)
        - 1963-74 (Box 191, Folder 50-59)
      - Affiliate Visits for Program Planning 1969 (Box 191, Folder 60)
      - Analysis of Fund Raising
        - 1971 (Box 191, Folder 61)
        - 1977 (Box 191)
      - Annual Meeting, Western Regional Meeting, Santa Barbara, CA 1980 (Box 191, Folder 62)
      - Bay Area Direct Mail Project
        - 1974 (Box 191, Folder 63)
        - 1975-78 (Box 191)
      - Capital Fund Drive Activities 1977 (Box 191, Folder 64)
      - Committees
        - 1975-78 (Box 191, Folder 65-67)
        - 1970-74 (Box 191, Folder 68)
        - Medical
          - 1976-78 (Box 191, Folder 69)
          - 1972-74 (Box 191, Folder 70)
          - 1975 (Box 191)
          - Minutes 1973 (Box 191, Folder 71)
      - Contract Counties 1963-71 (Box 192, Folder 1)
      - Consumer Advisory Committees (in Affiliates), Guidelines 1972 (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Organization Outline for Statewide Public Affairs Committees (Gatov-Kraus) 1973? (Box 192, Folder 3)
      - Western Region Planning Committee 1970-73 (Box 192, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence
        - Legal (Paul, Eve) 1978-79 (Box 192, Folder 5)
        - 1976-80 (Box 192, Folder 6-9)
        - Robert Webber, Director
          - 1975 (Box 192, Folder 10)
          - 1972-74 (Box 192, Folder 11-13)
        - Director 1971 (Box 192, Folder 14)
        - Francis X. Mayers, Director 1970 (Box 192, Folder 15)
        - Madrid T. Hamilton, Director 1965-69 (Box 192, Folder 16-19)
      - Doris Critz, Resources Consultant
        - 1973-74 (Box 192, Folder 20)
        - 1975 (Box 192)
      - Double Billing, HEW & Title IV 1973 (Box 192, Folder 21)
      - "Facts Needed to Support a Family Planning Project," R. Webber 1971 (Box 192, Folder 22)
      - Draft Regulations for Title IV, A 1972 (Box 192, Folder 23)
      - Funding for Family Planning, State & Federal 1974 (Box 192, Folder 24)
      - John Evants, Fund Raiser 1970-71 (Box 192, Folder 25)
      - Functional Accounting System: Computer Program 1974 (Box 192, Folder 26)
      - Health Maintenance Organizations (HMOS)
        - 1973-74 (Box 192, Folder 27)
        - 1977-78 (Box 192)
      - Leases, Correspondence
        - 1971-74 (Box 192, Folder 28)
        - 1976 (Box 192)
      - Memo to Executive Directors, Defective Diaphragm 1977 (Box 192, Folder 29)
      - Memos, Mimeos, General
        - 1971-74 (Box 192, Folder 30)
        - 1975-78 (Box 192)
  - General Regional Staff Meetings 1980 (Box 192, Folder 31)
  - California
    - Migrants 1971 (Box 192, Folder 32)
    - Personnel: Employment, Vacation, Leaves, Overtime, Termination, etc.
      - 1972-74 (Box 192, Folder 33)
      - 1975-78 (Box 192)
      - Personnel Survey Form for Executive Directors
        - 1971 (Box 192, Folder 34)
        - 1977 (Box 192)
    - Planning Team, John C. Robbins 1970 (Box 192, Folder 35)
    - Preliminary Report on Western Region Planning Project, Confidential 1970 (Box 192, Folder 36)
    - Minutes of Western Regional Planning Committee, Final Corrected Copy 1970 (Box 192, Folder 37)
    - California
      - Western Region Planning Project (National Planning Team Committee) 1970 (Box 192, Folder 38)
      - Jim Phegley, Corporate Fund Drive Solicitor 1972-73 (Box 192, Folder 39)
      - Pregnancy & Abortion
        - Counseling Project 1972 (Box 192, Folder 40)
        - Reports 1971-72 (Box 192, Folder 41)
        - Counseling 1970-71 (Box 192, Folder 42)
      - Preparing a Budget, Affiliates Considering Starting a Clinic, Suthers 1972 (Box 192, Folder 43)
      - Proceedings, Family Planning, Prejudice and Politics, Madrid T. Hamilton 1968 (Box 192, Folder 44)
      - Professional Education Training Center 1969 (Box 192, Folder 45)
      - Projects 1969, 1971 (Box 192, Folder 46)
      - Public Affairs
        - 1973-74 (Box 192, Folder 47)
        - 1975-77 (Box 192)
      - Publicity
        - 1963-74 (Box 192, Folder 48)
        - 1975-77 (Box 192)
      - Reports
        - Interim Report on Title 4A & Title 19, 1971 (Box 192, Folder 49)
        - Report to the Affiliation Committee 1972-73 (Box 192, Folder 50)
        - General
          - 1971-74 (Box 192, Folder 51)
          - 1975-80 (Box 192)
        - Madrid T. Hamilton, Director 1965-70 (Box 192, Folder 52-54)
        - Members
          - 1970-74 (Box 192, Folder 55)
          - 1977-78 (Box 192)
          - 1965-74 (Box 192, Folder 56)
      - Correspondence, Regional Chairman and/or Representative
        - 1970-74 (Box 192, Folder 57)
        - 1975-78 (Box 192)
      - Regional Representative's Reports
        - Annual Meetings 1974 (Box 192, Folder 58)
        - National Board & Executive Committee Meetings
          - 1974 (Box 192, Folder 59)
          - 1975-77 (Box 192)
          - 1972-73 (Box 192, Folder 60-61)
      - Regional Representatives Rep. Meetings 1970-71 (Box 192, Folder 62)
      - Regional Representatives Report of PPWP Executive Committee & Regional Rep. Mtgs. 1970 (Box 192, Folder 63)
      - Technical Assistance
        - 1968-72 (Box 192, Folder 64)
        - 1978 (Box 192)
      - Training Center for Family Planning 1969 (Box 192, Folder 65)
      - Service in Rural Area 1971 (Box 192, Folder 66)
      - Task Force 1978 (Box 192, Folder 67)
      - Transfer of Montana Affiliates to the Western Region 1975 (Box 192, Folder 68)
      - Volunteer and Staff Training 1976 (Box 192, Folder 69)
      - Volunteer Resource Pool
        - 1972-74 (Box 192, Folder 70)
        - 1975 (Box 192)
      - Workshops
        - Annual Meeting, Yakima, Washington 1979 (Box 192, Folder 71)
        - Spring Conference, Portland, Oregon 1978 (Box 192, Folder 72)
        - Annual Meeting, Los Angeles, California 1977 (Box 192, Folder 73)
  - Southeast Region
    - Georgia
      - Abortion, General, Correspondence
        - 1971-74 (Box 193, Folder 1)
        - 1975-78 (Box 193)
      - Affiliate, Resource Pool 1975-76 (Box 193, Folder 2)
      - Affiliation & Financial Data 1976-78 (Box 193, Folder 3-4)
        - 1974 (Box 193, Folder 5)
        - 1975 (Box 193)
        - 1969-73 (Box 193, Folder 6-10)
        - Russell H. Richardson, Director 1965-68 (Box 193, Folder 11-13)
      - Avalon Grant
        - Correspondence and Financial Data
          - 1965-68 (Box 193, Folder 14)
          - 1975-76 (Box 193)
        - Third Progress Report on the Avalon Foundation Grant for Expansion of Region 1966-67 (Box 193, Folder 15)
        - Fourth Progress Report on the Avalon Foundation Grant for Expansion of Region 1968 (Box 193, Folder 16)
      - Board Development Seminar 1977 (Box 193, Folder 17)
      - CDC Clinic Flow Studies (Center for Disease Control) 1977-78 (Box 193, Folder 18)
      - Certification Area/Turf Area of Affiliates in the Southeast Region 1974 (Box 193, Folder 19)
      - Committees
        - 1975-78 (Box 193, Folder 20-21)
        - 1971-74 (Box 193, Folder 22)
        - 1975 (Box 193)
        - Medical
          - 1977-78 (Box 193, Folder 23)
          - 1973-74 (Box 193, Folder 24)
          - 1975-76 (Box 193)
      - Correspondence
        - 1975-80 (Box 193, Folder 25-28)
        - Dorothy DuBois, Director 1973-74 (Box 193, Folder 29)
        - 1973 (Box 193, Folder 30)
        - Dorothy DuBois, Director 1972 (Box 193, Folder 31)
        - 1971 (Box 193, Folder 32)
        - Russell H. Richardson, Director 1964-70 (Box 193, Folder 33-39)
      - Discussion Papers: Location/Status of S.E. Region Office & Staff, "How Can Our Regional Offices Be More Effective," (Richardson, Suthers) 1976 (Box 193, Folder 40)
      - Executive Directors Conference 1977 (Box 193, Folder 41)
      - Expansion of Family Planning in the Rural South 1970 (Box 193, Folder 42)
      - Fund Raising Seminar 1972-73 (Box 193, Folder 43)
      - History & Development (A Brief Overview) 1973 (Box 193, Folder 44)
      - Alan F. Guttmacher Fund 1970 (Box 193, Folder 45)
      - Insurance Policies 1972 (Box 193, Folder 46)
      - Job Descriptions 1970-71 (Box 193, Folder 47)
      - Leases
        - 1973-74 (Box 193, Folder 48)
        - 1975-76 (Box 193)
      - Levi Strauss Training Program 1978 (Box 193, Folder 49)
      - Needs Assessment Seminar, Temporary Folder 1975 (Box 193, Folder 50)
      - Newsletter 1980 (Box 193, Folder 51)
      - Operating Guidelines 1978 (Box 193, Folder 52)
      - Papers, Russell H. Richardson 1964-68 (Box 193, Folder 53)
      - Peer Review 1977 (Box 193, Folder 54)
      - Personnel
        - Employment, Vacation, Leaves, Overtime, Termination, etc.
          - 1972-74 (Box 193, Folder 55)
          - 1975-78 (Box 193)
        - Survey of Southeast Region, Personnel Survey of Southeast Region Affiliates 1974 (Box 193, Folder 56)
      - Position Paper on Cuts in PPFA Budget, 6/18/77 1977 (Box 193, Folder 57)
      - Public Affairs
        - 1974 (Box 193, Folder 58)
        - 1975-78 (Box 193)
      - Publicity
        - 1964-74 (Box 193, Folder 59)
        - 1975-78 (Box 193)
      - Projects 1969 (Box 193, Folder 60)
      - Correspondence, Regional Chairman and/or Representative
        - 1970-74 (Box 193, Folder 61)
        - 1975-77 (Box 193)
      - Regional Representative's Report
        - PPFA Annual Meeting
          - 1974 (Box 193, Folder 62)
          - 1976 (Box 193)
          - 1971 (Box 193, Folder 63)
          - 1976-78 (Box 193)
        - PPWP Executive Committee & Regional Rep. Meetings 1970 (Box 193, Folder 64)
      - Annual Reports 1971-72 (Box 193, Folder 65)
      - Regional Representative's Report 1965-74 (Box 193, Folder 66-67)
      - Reports
        - General
          - 1973-74 (Box 193, Folder 68)
          - 1975-77 (Box 193)
          - Dorothy DuBois, Director 1972 (Box 193, Folder 69)
          - 1971-72 (Box 193, Folder 70-71)
          - R.R. Richardson, Director 1964-69 (Box 194, Folder 1-5)
        - Members
          - 1965-74 (Box 194, Folder 6)
          - 1976-78 (Box 194)
      - Rules of Procedure for the S.E. Region 1970 (Box 194, Folder 7)
      - Jan Schinning, Assistant Director of Resources 1972 (Box 194, Folder 8)
      - S.E.R. Executive Directors Association, (Sereda) 1978 (Box 194, Folder 9)
      - Services & Informational Material Provided to Affiliates in S.E. Region 1973 (Box 194, Folder 10)
      - Table of Organization 1973 (Box 194, Folder 11)
      - Technical Assistant
        - 1968-70 (Box 194, Folder 12)
        - 1975-78 (Box 194)
      - J. George Winders, Fund Raiser 1970-71 (Box 194, Folder 13)
      - Women's Caucus 1978 (Box 194, Folder 14)
      - Executive Directors
        - Personnel Meeting, Workshop 1978 (Box 194, Folder 15)
        - Meeting 1977 (Box 194, Folder 16)
        - Workshop, Asheville, North Carolina 1971 (Box 194, Folder 17)
        - Workshop 1969-70 (Box 194, Folder 18-19)
      - Workshops
        - S.E. Regional Conference, Memphis, Tenn., Hyatt Regency 1978 (Box 194, Folder 20)
        - S.E./Mid-Atlantic Regional Conferences, Richmond, Virginia 1977 (Box 194, Folder 21)
        - Regional Council Meeting, Atlanta, GA 1976 (Box 194, Folder 22)
        - Southeast Region Council Meeting, Charlotte, North Carolina
          - 1974 (Box 194, Folder 23)
          - 1975 (Box 194)
        - 10th Annual S.E. Region Council Meeting, Sarasota, Florida 1974 (Box 194, Folder 24)
        - S.E. Region Council Meeting, Nashville, Tenn. 1973 (Box 194, Folder 25)
        - 8th Annual S.E. Region Council Meeting, Columbia, S.C. 1971-72 (Box 194, Folder 26)
        - 7th Annual S.E. Region Council Meeting, Birmingham, Alabama 1970-71 (Box 194, Folder 27)
        - 5th Annual Council Meeting, Jacksonville 1968-69 (Box 194, Folder 28)
      - Family Planning Conference in Alabama 1968 (Box 194, Folder 29)
      - Workshops
        - 1972-74 (Box 194, Folder 30)
        - 1975-79 (Box 194)
        - 1968-69 (Box 194, Folder 31-32)
      - Family Planning Conference, Charleston, West Virginia 1967 (Box 194, Folder 33)
      - Design and Implementation of Family Planning, Tallahassee, Orlando, Miami 1967-68 (Box 194, Folder 34)
      - Workshops 1965-67 (Box 194, Folder 35)
  - Western Region
    - California
      - Workshops
        - Annual Meeting, Sacramento, California 1976 (Box 194, Folder 36)
        - Annual Meeting, Tuscon, Arizona
          - 1974 (Box 194, Folder 37)
          - 1975 (Box 194)
        - Spring Conference, Seattle, Washington 1974 (Box 194, Folder 38)
        - Palo Alto 1973 (Box 194, Folder 39)
        - Pasadena, California 1972 (Box 194, Folder 40)
        - Portland, Oregon 1971 (Box 194, Folder 41)
        - San Diego, California 1970 (Box 194, Folder 42)
        - President's & Board Members, Executive Director's 1972 (Box 194, Folder 43)
        - Madrid T. Hamilton, Director 1968 (Box 194, Folder 44)
        - Uniform Accounting 1967 (Box 194, Folder 45)
        - Miscellaneous Workshops 1975-78 (Box 194, Folder 46)
        - 1970-74 (Box 194, Folder 47)
        - 1975 (Box 194)
        - 1968-69 (Box 194, Folder 48)
      - Dr. Alan F. Guttmacher's Trip 1967-68 (Box 194, Folder 49)
      - Madrid T. Hamilton, Director 1965-67 (Box 194, Folder 50)
      - Miriam F. Garwood, Director
        - Correspondence 1963-68 (Box 194, Folder 51-52)
        - Reports, General 1965-67 (Box 194, Folder 53-54)
  - North Atlantic Region
    - New York
      - Abortion 1979 (Box 195, Folder 1)
      - Affiliation & Financial Data 1978-80 (Box 195, Folder 2)
      - Consultants 1978-79 (Box 195, Folder 3)
      - Medical Committee 1978-79 (Box 195, Folder 4)
      - Committees 1977-81 (Box 195, Folder 5)
      - North Atlantic Regional Council, Fall Meeting 1980-81 (Box 195, Folder 6)
      - Minutes of the North Atlantic Regional Council, Denver, Colorado 1980 (Box 195, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence 1978-81 (Box 195, Folder 8)
      - North Atlantic Region Directory 1978-81 (Box 195, Folder 9)
      - N.A.R. Executive Directors Council 1978-79 (Box 195, Folder 10)
      - Management Seminar, Seminar for Middle East Managers 1980 (Box 195, Folder 11)
      - Memos 1977-80 (Box 195, Folder 12)
      - Merger Plans, N.J. Affiliates 1978 (Box 195, Folder 13)
      - Newsletter 1978-80 (Box 195, Folder 14)
      - Operating Manual 1979 (Box 195, Folder 15)
      - North Atlantic Regional Plan 1978 (Box 195, Folder 16)
      - Personnel: Employment, Termination, Leave, Vacation, etc. 1977-81 (Box 195, Folder 17)
      - Public Affairs 1980 (Box 195, Folder 18)
      - Publicity 1979 (Box 195, Folder 19)
      - Regional Chairperson &/or Representative, Correspondence 1977-79 (Box 195, Folder 20)
      - Regional Representative's Grant 1978 (Box 195, Folder 21)
      - Regional Representative's Report
        - PPFA Annual Meetings 1978-79 (Box 195, Folder 22)
        - PPFA Executive Committee & Regional Reps. Meetings 1979-80 (Box 195, Folder 23)
        - National Board & Executive Committee Meetings 1977-80 (Box 195, Folder 24)
      - Reports
        - General 1978-81 (Box 195, Folder 25)
        - Members 1978-80 (Box 195, Folder 26)